[{"answer": "We make our own choices, we pay our own prices", "docId": "Bound.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "All part of the business", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What do you want", "docId": "Bound.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "A beer.  Of course", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "The redistribution of wealth", "docId": "Bound.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "I'm already in your bed", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Is that what her daddy tells her", "docId": "Bound.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "What are you saying?  That you don't have sex with men", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "For Christ's sake!  I heard you!  Thin walls, remember", "docId": "Bound.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "What the fuck was it", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Bound.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Like each other?  They hate each other", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I was getting out of the car when I saw him in the Mercedes", "docId": "Bound.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "It was him.  I'm positive", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Where is this going, my friend", "docId": "Bound.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Admit what", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "...  maybe three hours", "docId": "Bound.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "What do you think we're going to do? We have to find the money", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "What are you doing", "docId": "Bound.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Who are you going to call", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I was buzzing, I was knocking, but I guess you couldn't hear me on account of being in the shower", "docId": "Bound.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "That Violet is one nice lady.  Wish someone would help me relax", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "I started thinking maybe it's about the money so I call you, but all I get is the busy signal.  I figure the phone is off the hook, that's why I come rushing over here", "docId": "Bound.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Hey, if my friend was helping me relax, I'd probably do the same thing", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Hey, my friend, where's the key", "docId": "Bound.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Fuck it, I don't need the key", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "Violet, it's my friend and my friend.  They were in a car accident", "docId": "Bound.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "I think everything is okay", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "Now that's teamwork", "docId": "Bound.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "You know he would have done you, too", "qsentId": 30}]